I inadvertently upset y'all last night, but hear me out. I was watching Peaky Blinders
and there's a character who was going through a really difficult time and she was doing seances
and really like being in touch with her spiritual side that was making her son uncomfortable
and he couldn't get to her to help her deal with the dark things that she was actually dealing with
and Tommy Shelby told him, Michael, the spirits the mother sees are real. The ghosts she sees are real
and until you believe that they are real too, you won't be able to help her. This is what it is for
the people in this country who are disenchanted and apathetic about voting. So many of you are out
here just telling them how dumb they are. Until you see the reality of why they feel this way,
you will not be able to help them or us. And trust me, I understand your frustration. I was you.
But you have to get over yourself in order to see what is true and what is not. You have to get out
of your own way. And sometimes you get out of your own way and you're like, no, no, no, this is some
bulls**t. But sometimes you get out of your own way and other people's perspectives are revealed to
you. And when you see their perspectives, you understand because of your humanity that it's not
about proving that you're right. You have now transcended into a process of how do we work
together to get all of us right.